bedroomproducersblog.com 2019-06-24

# Privacy Policy - Bedroom Producers Blog

Bedroom Producers Blog respects your privacy. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

When signing up for our mailing list or entering a contest/giveaway on our website, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your email address or other details.

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter or enter a giveaway or a promotion on our website..

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you sign up for our newsletter or enter a giveaway on our website in the following ways: 

  * To administer a contest, promotion or other site feature.
  * To send periodic emails as part of our weekly newsletter.

**How do we protect visitor information?**

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. We use regular Malware Scanning. We only provide articles and information, we never ask for personal or private information like credit card numbers.

**Do we use ‘cookies’?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For example, we use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We also use cookies to keep track of advertisements.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Google Chrome) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

**Third party disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. We do not give our e-mail lists out to other parties.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Opting out**

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

**How does our website handle do not track signals?**

We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. Users can visit our site anonymously.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us through our [contact form](https://bedroomproducersblog.com/contact).

Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes on this page.

_Last edited February 25th, 2015._
